[
  [
    {
      "question": "Which club has won the UEFA Champions League 14 times?",
      "answers": [
        "AC Milan",
        "Liverpool FC",
        "Real Madrid CF",
        "FC Bayern Munich"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Real Madrid CF"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which team has won the FIFA World Cup 5 times?",
      "answers": [
        "Italy",
        "Brazil",
        "Argentina",
        "France"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Brazil"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which club has won the UEFA Champions League in 2023?",
      "answers": [
        "Manchester City",
        "Inter Milan",
        "Real Madrid CF",
        "AC Milan"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Manchester City"
    }
  ],
  [
    {
      "question": "Which player has won the Ballon d'Or 8 times?",
      "answers": [
        "Cristiano Ronaldo",
        "Luka Modric",
        "Ronaldo Nazario",
        "Lionel Messi"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Lionel Messi"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which club has won the Premier League 20 times?",
      "answers": [
        "Liverpool FC",
        "Manchester United",
        "Manchester City",
        "Everton"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Manchester United"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which player has won the UEFA Champions League 5 times?",
      "answers": [
        "Lionel Messi",
        "Cristiano Ronaldo",
        "Neymar JR",
        "Sergio Ramos"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Cristiano Ronaldo"
    }
  ],
  [
    {
      "question": "Which club has won the LaLiga 35 times?",
      "answers": [
        "Atletico Madrid",
        "FC Barcelona",
        "Real Madrid CF",
        "Athletic Club"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Real Madrid CF"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which club has won the Serie A 36 times?",
      "answers": [
        "Juventus FC",
        "AC Milan",
        "Inter Milan",
        "AS Roma"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Juventus FC"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which club has won the FIFA Club World Cup 5 times?",
      "answers": [
        "FC Barcelona",
        "FC Bayern Munich",
        "Real Madrid CF",
        "Manchester City"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Real Madrid CF"
    }
  ],
  [
    {
      "question": "Which team has won the UEFA European Championship in 2016?",
      "answers": [
        "Italy",
        "Spain",
        "England",
        "Portugal"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Portugal"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which team has won the Copa America in 2021?",
      "answers": [
        "Brazil",
        "Argentina",
        "Uruguay",
        "Chile"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Argentina"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which team has won the UEFA Nations League in 2019?",
      "answers": [
        "France",
        "Spain",
        "Switzerland",
        "Portugal"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Portugal"
    }
  ],
  [
    {
      "question": "Which player has won the FIFA The Best in 2017?",
      "answers": [
        "Luka Modric",
        "Cristiano Ronaldo",
        "Lionel Messi",
        "Robert Lewandowski"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Cristiano Ronaldo"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which club has won the Bundesliga 33 times?",
      "answers": [
        "Hamburger SV",
        "Borussia Dortmund",
        "FC Schalke 04",
        "FC Bayern Munich"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "FC Bayern Munich"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which team has won the FIFA World Cup in 2018?",
      "answers": [
        "Spain",
        "France",
        "Uruguay",
        "Brazil"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "France"
    }
  ],
  [
    {
      "question": "Which club has won the UEFA Champions League in 2015?",
      "answers": [
        "FC Barcelona",
        "Juventus FC",
        "FC Bayern Munich",
        "Real Madrid CF"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "FC Barcelona"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which country has hosted the FIFA World Cup in 2010?",
      "answers": [
        "Italy",
        "Qatar",
        "Spain",
        "South Africa"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "South Africa"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which player has won the FIFA Club World Cup 6 times?",
      "answers": [
        "Sergio Ramos",
        "Toni Kroos",
        "Lionel Messi",
        "Xavi"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Toni Kroos"
    }
  ],
  [
    {
      "question": "Which club has won the UEFA Europa League 5 times?",
      "answers": [
        "Sevilla FC",
        "Atletico Madrid",
        "Juventus FC",
        "Liverpool FC"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Sevilla FC"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which team has won the UEFA European Championship in 2008 & 2012?",
      "answers": [
        "Italy",
        "Portugal",
        "Spain",
        "Netherlands"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Spain"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which club has won UEFA Super Cup 5 times?",
      "answers": [
        "Atletico Madrid",
        "Liverpool FC",
        "Chelsea FC",
        "FC Barcelona"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "FC Barcelona"
    }
  ],
  [
    {
      "question": "Which player has won the Ballon d'Or in 2019?",
      "answers": [
        "Cristiano Ronaldo",
        "Lionel Messi",
        "Karim Benzema",
        "Ronaldinho"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Lionel Messi"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which team has won the FIFA World Cup only once?",
      "answers": [
        "England",
        "Uruguay",
        "France",
        "Argentina"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "England"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which manager has won the Premier League 13 times?",
      "answers": [
        "Arsene Wenger",
        "Pep Guardiola",
        "Jose Mourinho",
        "Sir Alex Ferguson"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Sir Alex Ferguson"
    }
  ],
  [
    {
      "question": "Which player was the top scorer of FIFA World Cup 2022?",
      "answers": [
        "Olivier Giroud",
        "Kylian Mbappe",
        "Alvaro Morata",
        "Lionel Messi"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Kylian Mbappe"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which team has won the UEFA Nations League in 2023?",
      "answers": [
        "Portugal",
        "France",
        "Spain",
        "Croatia"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Spain"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which player is the all-time top goal scorer of UEFA Champions League?",
      "answers": [
        "Robert Lewandowski",
        "Karim Benzema",
        "Lionel Messi",
        "Cristiano Ronaldo"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Cristiano Ronaldo"
    }
  ],
  [
    {
      "question": "Which club has won the UEFA Europa League in 2022?",
      "answers": [
        "Sevilla FC",
        "Chelsea FC",
        "Eintracht Frankfurt",
        "Villarreal FC"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Eintracht Frankfurt"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which team has won the FIFA World Cup 4 times?",
      "answers": [
        "Spain",
        "Germany",
        "France",
        "Argentina"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Germany"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which club has won the UEFA Champions League 7 times?",
      "answers": [
        "AC Milan",
        "Liverpool FC",
        "FC Barcelona",
        "FC Bayern Munich"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "AC Milan"
    }
  ]
]